

E-mail vulaflori@gmail.com

Phone +383 44 390 535

Website www.florivula.github.io/Portfolio/

Address Besim Bistrazhini, Gjakovë

PROJECTS

• 2023 | IntegrohuKS

Launched a job-searching website that connected the youth of Kosovo with employers

2023 | EasyOrder

Currently working on a powerful point of sale web application which offers a simple and efficient way for businesses to manage their sales, inventory, and customer data.

SKILLS

Time management



• • •



LANGUAGES

Albanian

• • • • • • C

English

• • • • • • • C2

FLORI VULA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Dedicated young professional, currently studying towards becoming a Software Engineer. Quite experienced and very knowledgeable in programming. I am very efficient and organized. I am hard-working and keen to learn new things. I am focused and time-oriented, so meeting deadlines is a top priority for me. I am also a team player and enjoy being in an environment where people share mutual respect and the desire to help each other.

EDUCATION

2020-2021 ANDROID DEVELOPERS

I Developed a collection of apps, starting my journey as an Android developer using Kotlin.

2021-2024 UNIVERSITY FOR BUSINESS AND TECHNOLOGY

| Majoring in "Computer Science and Engineering". Expected Bachelor's degree completion date: July/2024

SOFTWARE

Proficient in many programming languages, in which i combine technical expertise and design skills for innovative software solutions and user-friendly interfaces.









WORK EXPERIENCE

2021-2022 | Graphic Designer & Social Media Manager - "OK"

At OK fast food, I served as a Graphic Designer and Social Media Manager, creating visually compelling content and managing online presence to enhance brand engagement and awareness.

2017-2019 | Graphic Designer Editor - "Dukagjini Publishing"

At Dukagjini Publishing, I played a pivotal role in the production of children's school books by serving as an Editor. My responsibilities included meticulously reviewing and correcting errors identified by the proofreading team, ensuring the highest quality educational materials for young learners.